字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
最快首发美剧日剧下载请登录
字幕组网站www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译：王大可 Reginamoon Charl 木浅薰 想名字好难
翻译：dzysteven 小酸奶 JohnnyG   校对：油炸电风扇   木浅薰
时间轴：biubiubiu  浪浪浪  酥酥酥
后期：斯人      总监：某羽
诉 讼 双 雄
第六季   第八集
《诉讼双雄》前情提要
你的处决日期已经定下来了
Your execution date has been set.
-什么时候  -三十天后
- When? - 30 days.
你说过你会找到玛利亚
You said you were gonna find Maria.
你们有一周时间来找到证人
You have one week to find a witness.
一周后  他的行刑日期就不会再变了
After that, his execution date is set in stone.
我们已经找到那个向萨特提供信息的人了
We found the guy who's been feeding Sutter his information.
菲利普・亚伦  我知道
Phillip Allen. I know.
两个小时前他来找我签协议
He came by to cut a deal two hours ago,
我跟他签了
so I gave him one.
-不  你没有  -冷静
- No you goddamn didn't. - Relax.
就证监会而言  迈克直接指向那位证人
As far as the SEC is concerned, Mike lead directly
这将让那个该死的混蛋的余生
to the witness who's gonna put that piece of shit away
都在监狱中悲惨的度过
for the rest of his life.
但你只有一个短暂的机会  可以向证监会自首
You have a small window to come clean with the SEC
以免牢狱之灾
and save yourself.
我不会背叛我父亲
I would never turn on my own father.
我不是为了那个杂种进了监狱
I didn't take this deal for that son of a bitch.
我进来是为了我很爱的妻子
I took it for my wife.
如果你再未经我的允许找她
And if you ever contact her again without my blessing,
我对天发誓我会痛扁你
I swear to God, I will beat the shit out of you.
吉米・罗杰斯找到了你们要找的失踪的证人
Jim Rogers found your missing witness.
她三年前去世了
She died three years ago.
你要告发你的室友
You're informing on your roommate.
我很清楚  你不快点把我弄出去
I know it, and if you don't get me out of here soon,
你的室友也要知道了
your bunkmate's gonna know it, too.
他们取消了与迈克的交易
They pulled Mike's deal.
真该死  是我逼他投向了你们
Goddamn it, I drove that guy to you!
但如果我把事情告诉他们
If I tell them that,
他们就会发现我们动过手脚
they're gonna know what we did.
肖恩  求你了  一定还有
Sean, please, there's got to be
别的办法能达到目的
another way to make this happen.
抱歉  哈维  恐怕没有
I'm sorry, Harvey, there isn't.
杰西卡  我能和你聊两句吗
Jessica, can I talk to you for a second?
哈维  能等等吗
Harvey, can it wait?
我刚得知了一个死刑案的坏消息
I just got some bad news about our death row case.
不行
No, it can't.
-卡荷尔刚刚取消了迈克的协议  -什么
- Cahill just pulled Mike's deal. - What?
我以为他是个言出必行的人
I thought he was a man of his word.
他说不是他
He's saying it wasn't him.
是他的领导干的  但这有什么区别呢
It was his superiors, but what difference does it make?
当然有区别
It makes all the difference in the world,
如果是他做的  那你可以越过他上报
because if it's him, you can go over his head.
如果我越过他
I go over his head,
那所有人都知道我们是串通的了
everybody knows we're in on this thing together.
所以你的意思是
So what you're telling me is,
不仅迈克的协议被取消了
not only are they pulling Mike's deal,
你还毫无意义地输了一个案子
but you're going to lose this case for nothing?
是的
Yeah.
差不多就这个意思
I guess that's what I'm telling you.
那你肯定不想听到我要说的这些话
Then you're not gonna like what I have to say.
如果迈克出不来
But if Mike's not getting out,
-也许你应该赢了案子  -什么
- you might as well win. - What?
哈维  我们现在正在重整旗鼓
Harvey, we're in the middle of building ourselves back up.
如果你输了这场官司  我们就回到起点了
You lose this case, we take it in the knee.
杰西卡  这个人犯罪了
Jessica, the guy is guilty.
但你是他的律师
And you're his goddamn lawyer.
接了这个案子
And you took this case.
如果不是为了救迈克出来
And I never would have taken it
我根本不会接这个案子
if it wasn't to get Mike out.
但你确实接了
Well, you did take it.
这也将把我们打回原点
And if it's just gonna kick us back down the mountain,
我不在乎你用什么手段
then I don't care what it takes.
赢下这场官司
You win that goddamn case.
我们现在开始审理公诉人
We're gathered to hear the United States
对威廉・萨特内幕交易指控的案件
versus William Sutter on the charges of insider trading.
公诉人准备好进行开庭陈述了吗
Is the prosecution prepared to deliver its opening statement?
准备好了  法官大人
We are, Your Honor.
陪审团的各位女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
威廉・萨特近几十年
William Sutter has been earning outrageous returns
赚取了巨额的财富
for decades.
我相信辩方律师会试图
Now, I'm sure the defense is going to try to
说服你们萨特先生是凭借他的勇气
convince you Mr. Sutter trades with his gut
和直觉或是一些无法证实的神秘力量
or his instinct or some mysterious explanation
来进行交易的
that is impossible to verify.
但这并不是他财富的来源
But that isn't how he makes his money.
我们也可以证明这点
And we can prove it.
我们有一位证人记录了
We have a witness that can document giving
近十年他如何对威廉・萨特
inside information to William Sutter time
一次又一次的提供内幕消息
and time again over the last ten years.
当我们把这个证人带到你们面前后
And when we present that witness to you,
你们一定会跳起来
you'll be leaping out of your chair to convict
想要将这个人定罪
that man beyond a reasonable doubt.
斯佩克特先生
Mr. Specter.
他说的证人是什么意思
What the hell witness is he talking about?
这种事情不是应该要提前告知吗
Didn't it have to be in discovery?
他确实应该那样做
It sure as hell did.
你要怎么做
What're you gonna do about it?
我要阻止他那样做
I'm gonna stop it dead in its tracks.
斯佩克特先生
Mr. Specter,
辩方准备好进行开庭陈述了吗
is the defense ready to deliver its opening statement?
没有  法官大人  但我们准备好要求
No, Your Honor, but we are ready to request
进行三天的延迟了
an immediate three-day delay of these proceedings.
以什么理由
On what grounds?
公诉人知道理由
The prosecution knows what grounds,
因为他刚刚违反了告知原则
because he just violated the rules of discovery.
法官大人
Your Honor,
我不知道他在说什么
I have absolutely no idea what he's talking about.
你知道  因为你刚刚在开庭陈述中
Yes, you do because you just introduced a witness
引入了一位证人
into your opening statement
我们之前从来没有听说过这个证人
and this is the first I'm hearing about it.
你之所以之前从来没有听说过这个证人
It's the first you're hearing about it
是因为这个证人昨天才出现
because the witness just came forward yesterday.
对不起  难道互联网瘫痪了吗
I'm sorry, did the Internet go down?
你的套餐流量用完了吗
Did you go over the limit on your friends and family plan?
因为你应该通知我们的
Because we're required to be notified
但我现在连这个人的名字都不知道
and I don't even know what this person's name is.
他叫菲利普・亚伦  他准备好
His name is Phillip Allen and he's prepared
要将那个人送到他该在的监狱里了
to put that man behind bars where he belongs.
卡荷尔先生  够了
Mr. Cahill, that's enough.
法官大人  我们需要三天时间对证人取证
Your Honor, we need three days to depose this witness.
这太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
他们知道自己要输了  这只是在拖延时间
They've lost, they know it, and they're just trying to stall.
那你在我的法庭上抛下这枚重磅炸弹之前
Then you should have thought of that before you decided
就该想到这点
to drop this bomb in my courtroom.
斯佩克特先生  给你三天时间
Mr. Specter, you have three days.
我没想到会这么快再见到你们
I wasn't expecting you so soon.
我们有些消息想当面告诉你
We have some news we wanted to give you in person.
我们找到玛利亚・戈麦斯了
We found Maria Gomez.
伦纳德  她三年前去世了
Leonard, she died three years ago.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
意思是我们还有五天时间再去
It means that we have five more days to find
找一些有用的信息让你的案子重审
something we can use to get your case re-opened.
听起来像在用一种婉转的方式跟我说三十天后
That sounds like a polite way of telling me that in 30 days,
我就会死
I'm gone.
如果我们能有不止五天时间呢
And what if there was a way to get us more than five days?
那就抓住机会啊
Let's take it.
你在行刑时有权要求
You have the right to have a family member
一位家庭成员到场
present at your execution.
如果你有以为生病的亲属
If you have a relative that's sick,
需要康复以后才能赶来
who needs time to get better to travel,
我们就可以向法院请求延期
we can petition the court for a delay
而且他们必须同意
and they have to grant it.
我姨妈哈莉特  是她把我拉扯大的
The woman who raised me, my Aunt Harriet.
她患有多发性硬化症
She has MS.
但这也没什么用
But that's not gonna do us any good,
因为她不想和我扯上任何关系
because she doesn't want anything to do with me.
她从没来探视过你吗
She never came to visit you?
她觉得我是有罪的
She thinks I'm guilty.
说我让家族蒙羞了
Says I brought shame on the family.
就算这是真的  你如今也需要她
Even if you did, you need her now.
她必须明白这一点
She has to see that.
我联系过她  瑞秋
I reached out to her, Rachel,
我刚进来的那一年里联系了她无数次
a thousand times my first years here.
我写信告诉她  我最最需要的就是
I wrote her that there's nothing I needed
知道她是支持我的
more than to know that I had her support.
可既然她当时就没有支持我...
She didn't give it to me then, and...
现在也不会
she's not gonna give it to me now.
如果她知道
Well, maybe if she could see that
我们这样的人都相信你
two women like us believe in you,
她说不定也就会相信你了
then she'll be able to believe in you, too.
如果你们真能让她相信我
If you can make that happen,
那对我而言比什么都重要
that would mean the world to me.
我们会让她相信你的
Then we'll make that happen.
你刚刚那招很厉害啊
That was nice work in there.
我觉得这足以让我们争取到无效审判了
Think it was good enough to get us a mistrial?
无效审判
Mistrial?
你该庆幸他们刚才没直接判你有罪
You're lucky they didn't find you guilty after that.
你在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
别再糊弄我了  威廉
Enough bullshit, William.
这次不是证监会问你了  而是我问你
This isn't the SEC asking anymore, this is me.
菲利普・亚伦是谁
Who the hell is Phillip Allen
他又准备告诉他们些什么
and what the hell is he gonna tell them?
他是个投资银行家  曾经在我手下工作
He's an investment banker, used to work for me.
他不会和他们说任何关于我的事的
He's not gonna tell them shit about me
因为他完全不知道我的事
because he doesn't know shit about me.
那在他们说他是证人时你为何如此惊讶
Then why were you so surprised when they said they had him?
因为他能说我女儿的事
Because he can tell them about my daughter.
我明白了
I get it.
他把内部消息透露给她
He gives inside information to her,
所以假如东窗事发了
so if this goes down,
出事的就是她而不是你
she goes down instead of you.
不会有人出事的
No one's going down.
因为他们无法证明
'Cause they can't prove
她把他透露给她的消息告诉了我
she told me what he told her.
也就是说  假如你做好你的工作
Which means, if you do your job,
我俩就没事了
we both get off.
威廉  你这是在冒个大险
William, you're taking a huge risk.
你以为我雇你这样一个枪手是干什么用的
What the hell you think I hired a gunslinger like you for?
所以别再告诉我赢不了
So stop telling me I can't win
好好工作  开始赢吧
and go ahead and start winning.
你每早都吃鸡蛋
You keep eating eggs every morning,
会得心脏病的
you're gonna have a heart attack.
你没听说吗
Didn't you hear?
现在鸡蛋又对人体有益了
They're good for you now.
假如五年之后
What happens five years from now
又变成有害了呢
when they become bad for you again?
你是担心我会出事吗
Worried something's gonna happen to me?
我是担心自己得应付个新室友
I'm worried I'm gonna have to deal with another roommate.
我花了好长一段时间才适应了你
Took me long enough to get used to you.
凯文...
Kevin...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
都过去了
Water under the bridge.
你是为了我着想
All right? You had my best interest in mind.
要培根吗
You want some bacon?
这玩意无论何时都是对人体有益的
Man, that's always gonna be good for you.
同意  老弟
Amen to that, brother.
瞧瞧这是谁  俩基友啊
Look who it is. Frick and Frack.
我们正在谈话呢  加洛
We're in the middle of a conversation, Gallo.
可不是嘛
Oh, I bet you are.
迈克真是一位很棒的倾听者  是不是  凯文
Mike here's an excellent listener, isn't he, Kevin?
-你想要什么  -什么都不要
- What do you want? - Nothing.
就是看你俩关系这么好我心里高兴
It's just nice to see you guys are such good friends.
很高兴看到你俩能相互信任
Nice to know you can trust each other.
我只希望自己能信任
I only wish I could trust that
迈克是真的在帮我争取假释
Mike here was really working on getting me out on parole.
我们在争取
We are working on it.
你们快没时间了
Well, you're running out of time.
你听我说好吗  加洛
Would you listen to me, Gallo?
不  没什么好听的
No, there's no listening!
你今晚六点之前必须把哈维找来这里
You got until 6:00 tonight to get Harvey down here
不然的话
or after that,
我就自己安排一个听证会
I'm gonna schedule a little hearing of my own.
-我能帮到你什么吗  -我希望如此
- Can I help you? - I hope so.
我是瑞秋・赞恩
My name's Rachel Zane.
我是你外甥案子的律师
And I'm a lawyer working on your nephew's case.
我外甥的案子很早以前就结了
My nephew's case was over a long time ago.
谢天谢地
And thank God for that.
女士
Ma'am.
我来这是因为我们相信
I'm here because we believe
伦纳德是被冤枉的
Leonard was wrongly convicted of those murders.
他们都这么狡辩的  不是吗
Well, that's what they all say, isn't it?
但是就因为他愚弄了你
But just because he suckered you,
不意味着他能愚弄我
doesn't mean he's gonna sucker me.
他没有愚弄谁
He didn't sucker anyone.
我看了证据  我逐渐了解了他
I looked at the evidence and I got to know the man.
所以你有证据证明他没杀人吗
So you got proof he didn't do it?
我们正在努力
We're working on it.
但假如我们无法找到办法推后处决
But if we can't find a way to push back the execution,
那么在三十天之后这一切就都没意义了
then in 30 days it won't matter anymore.
你想要我怎么做
What do you want from me?
我希望你能请求法院延期
I want you to ask the court for a delay
好让你在他被处决时陪着他
so you can be with him at his execution.
我不会去看他被处决的
I'm not gonna watch him die.
迪恩女士  求你了
Ms. Deon, please.
是你把他带大的
You raised him.
伦纳德十四岁到十七岁是我带的
I raised Leonard from when he was 14 to 17.
我接纳了他  用心爱他
I took him in, I loved him,
他过去就不是什么好人  现在也不是
He was no good then and he's no good now.
既然如此
Well, if that's the case,
你就不用去看处决了
you don't have to be at the execution.
但假如你能签了这份请愿
But if you could sign this request
表明自己这个月太虚弱  不能长途跋涉
that says you're too infirm to travel this month,
这至少能给他一个机会证明你错了
it will at least give him the chance to prove you wrong.
我会签了这份请愿的
I'll sign your letter.
但我不会去看他被处决的
But I'm not watching him die.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你在这里呢
There you are.
我一早上都坐立不安
I've been on pins and needles all morning.
晚餐如何
How was dinner?
完完全全是一场闹剧  唐娜
It was a complete and total shit show, Donna.
路易  发生什么事了
Louis, what happened?
发生的事情是
What happened was,
我发现我的梦中女神有主了
I found out the woman of my dreams is spoken for.
-她结婚了  -也有可能
- She's married? - She might as well be.
她有个住在加州的长期男友
She has this long-term boyfriend who lives in California
他们互相允许对方和别人约会
and they have this arrangement where they see other people.
即便如此  这也是我一生中最美妙的一晚
And even though it was the most wonderful night of my life,
我要继续前进了
I'm moving on.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你一生中最美妙的一晚
The most wonderful night of your life?
你到底为什么还要留在那里吃完晚餐啊
Why did you even stay through dinner?
因为她说我是唯一一个
Because she gave me some line about being the only person
和她这样做的人
she'd ever done this with.
但如今我回过头来想想
But now that I think about it,
这又能改变什么呢
what the hell difference does that make?
我觉得这能改变一切
I think it makes all the difference in the world.
什么意思
What're you talking about?
路易  假如你真的是唯一一个
Louis, if you're really the only man
和她这样做过的人
she's ever done this with,
那这就意味着你有
then that means you've got something
那个男人没有的东西
that this other man doesn't have.
你怎么知道
How could you know that?
他们在一起三年
They've been together three years.
我比不了
I can't compete with that.
因为人幸福的时候
Because when you're happy,
不会去想别的
you don't go looking somewhere else.
唐娜
Donna--
路易  我告诉过你我跟米歇尔分手
Louis, I told you I broke up with Mitchell,
但是没有告诉你为什么
but I didn't tell you why.
他移情别恋了
He wanted to see other people.
他想搬来跟我一起住
He wanted to move in with me.
当他提出来  我开始想象跟他一起的生活
And when he asked me, I started picturing a life with him.
我就知道他不是我的真命天子
And that's when I knew he wasn't the right one for me.
我怎么知道我是她的命中注定
How can I know I'm the one for her?
你无法知道
You can't.
但是如果你不努力  就永远不会知道
But you'll never know if you don't fight for her.
哈维・斯佩克特办公室
Harvey Specter's office.
丹伯里联邦监狱有人向你致电
You have a call from Danbury Federal Prison.
-你是否愿意  -愿意
- Do you accept-- - Yes.
唐娜  是我  我得跟他谈谈
Donna, it's me, I need to talk to him.
他不在  迈克  他在法庭上
I don't have him, Mike, he's in court.
我不在乎他在哪里
I don't care where he is.
我得知道加洛的保释听证会怎么样了
I need to know what's going on with Gallo's parole hearing.
没怎么样
Nothing's going on.
没怎么样是什么意思
What the hell do you mean "Nothing's going on"?
哈维想着在他去做之前
Harvey was hoping that you were gonna be out of there
你就能出来了
before he had to go through with it.
该死的  唐娜
Goddamn it, Donna,
加洛知道我跟卡荷尔的事了
Gallo knows about me and Cahill.
如果他今天看不到进展
If he doesn't see some progress by the end of the day,
他就会去告诉凯文
he's gonna tell Kevin.
迈克  哈维还不想告诉你  但是
Mike, Harvey didn't want you to know this yet, but...
你跟卡荷尔之间没什么事了
there is no you and Cahill.
-什么  -卡荷尔取消了你的协议
- What? - Cahill pulled your deal.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
他的上司说
His superiors said
你没有兑现你的承诺
you didn't hold up your end of the bargain.
胡说八道
That is bullshit!
我忙前忙后就是为了实现承诺
I've been busting my ass to hold up my end of the bargain.
我知道  哈维也知道
I know that and Harvey knows that,
他正在努力把你的协议要回来
and he's trying to get your deal back.
你去告诉他
Well, you tell him that while he's getting around
在他想要让卡荷尔说话算话的时候
to making Cahill honor his goddamn word,
或许可以花点时间履行自己做出的承诺
maybe he could take just a minute to honor his word
把加洛该死的保释听证会弄好
and get Gallo his goddamn parole hearing.
-我拿到了  -她签了吗
- I got it. - She signed it?
签了  还有她医生的宣誓证词
She did, and an affidavit from her doctor, too.
好的  我会去法庭把这件事搞定
All right, I'll go to court and make this happen.
你赶紧把我们手上的每一份证据都看一遍
You start going back through every piece of evidence we have
尽管这给了我们一丝喘息的机会去找证据
because this gives us some breathing room
但我们还是得找到才行
to find something, but we have to deliver.
-杰西卡  -听着  瑞秋
- Jessica... - Look, Rachel,
我知道你想跟我一起出庭
I know you want to go to court with me,
但是我们没有时间
but we don't have the time--
-不  我不是想说这个  -那是什么
- No, that's not it. - Well, then what is it?
她虽然签了申请  但是
She signed the request, but...
她并没有真的同意来见他
she wouldn't actually agree to be there with him if--
瑞秋
Rachel.
我们的工作不是当最坏的结果发生时
It's not our job to reunite him with his family
为他重系亲情
if it comes to it.
而是确保不让最坏的情况发生
It is our job to make sure it doesn't come to it.
我是说她不想来
I meant she doesn't want to come
是因为她认为他有罪
because she thinks that he did it.
如果我们没办法让他自己的姨妈相信他无辜
And if we can't convince his own aunt that he's innocent,
我们要怎么说服十二个陌生人
how are we gonna convince 12 strangers?
现在我更看重的是
Right now, I'd rather focus on the fact that
我们多给了他三十天来拯救自己
we're getting the man another 30 days to save his life.
迈克  坐下
Mike, sit down.
我得跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
卡荷尔昨天取消我的协议的时候
You needed to talk to me yesterday
你就该跟我谈谈了
when Cahill decided to pull my deal.
他说是他上面的人
He's saying it was the people above him.
我当时不想
And I didn't want to tell you about it
没有想好解决方案就告诉你
until I figured out how to get it back.
你不告诉我的事情
Yeah, well the amount of things you're not telling me
真的开始越来越多了
are really starting to pile up.
我知道你发现了加洛的事情
I know you found out about Gallo.
对不起
I'm sorry.
但是我向你保证  我已经在解决了
But I give you my word, it's being taken care of.
就像解决我的协议一样吗
Oh, like my deal was being taken care of?
听我说
Listen to me.
我会解决菲利普・亚伦
I'm gonna neutralize Phillip Allen
这样你还是有机会从这里出去
so you still have a chance to walk out of here.
但你要是不能让吉尔・米勒出来指正她爸
But that's not gonna happen if you don't get Jill Miller
这一切都白费了
to testify against her father.
该死的  哈维  我已经试过了
Goddamn it, Harvey, I've been down that road.
吉尔是不会这样做的  凯文也不会
Jill's not gonna go for it and neither is Kevin.
那你最好想办法逼他
Well, then you better figure out a way to make him,
因为一旦我搞定菲利普・亚伦
because once I blow Phillip Allen out of the water,
卡荷尔下一个要找的就是凯文的老婆
the next person up on Cahill's hit list is Kevin's wife.
-你好  -塔拉
- Hello? - Hey, Tara.
是我  路易・利特
It's me, Louis Litt.
我知道你是谁  路易
I know who you are, Louis,
你不用连名带姓一起说
you don't have to use your last name.
我只是不想自以为是
Well, I don't like to be presumptuous.
你可能有另一个男人  我是说
I mean, you can have another man--I mean--
你可能认识其他叫路易的人
you can have another Louis in your life.
说到其他男人  路易
Speaking of other men, Louis.
我很高兴你回了电话
I'm glad you called back.
我那天晚上很开心
I had an amazing time the other night,
不过我不确定你能不能接受
but I wasn't sure you were okay with
我跟你说的我有
what I told you about me having a--
拜托  塔拉  这都2016年了
Oh, please, Tara, it's 2016.
如果一个男人不能接受他的女人跟其他人约会
If a man can't be okay with his woman seeing other men,
那苏珊・安东尼之前的奋斗是为了什么
then what was Susan B. Anthony even fighting for?
如果是这样的话  路易・利特
Well in that case, Louis Litt,
今晚约吗
how'd you like to go out tonight?
今晚
Tonight?
乐意之至
I'd love to.
那你告诉我地点
Then tell me where to be,
我七点准时去找你
and I'll meet you there at 7:00 p.m. sharp.
好的
Okay.
杰西卡・皮尔逊上庭
Jessica Pearson in court.
我可是很久没见到了
I haven't seen that in a while.
我喜欢时不时上场活动一下
I like to get back in the ring from time to time.
那你今天要兼并哪家大公司
So what giant companies are you merging today?
钢铁巨怪和环球万物吗
Behemoth Steel and Global Everything?
那是星期二的事
That was Tuesday.
今天  我是来救人一命的
Today, I am here to save a man's life.
我们接了一个"无罪计划"的案子
We took over an Innocence Project case.
"无罪计划"
Innocence Project?
你是想做什么  重塑你们公司的形象吗
So what're you trying to do, rehabilitate your firm's image?
我想做的事帮助一个人伸张正义
What I'm trying to do is help a man get justice.
如果这样能提升公司形象  那就更好了
And if doing that helps my firm look good, even better.
说得好
Fair enough.
你过得怎么样  杰夫
How have you been, Jeff?
挺好
I've been good.
我知道我说等这件事过去
Listen, I know we talked about me looking you up
我会去看你  但是
when this whole mess was over, but...
-我想告诉你  -没事  杰西卡
- I want you to know-- - It's okay, Jessica.
我理解
I understand.
不
No.
我是说  还没过去
What I mean is, it's not over.
我还在解决中
I'm still in it.
你真的是在努力重塑形象啊
You really are fighting to rehabilitate your image,
对吗
aren't you?
没错
I am.
很高兴见到你  杰西卡
It was good to see you, Jessica.
我也是  杰夫
It's good to see you too, Jeff.
你来干什么  肖恩
What're you doing here, Sean?
我来保护我的主要证人
I'm here to protect my star witness.
他有自己的律师
He's got his own attorney for that.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我们是来这里让你收集证据的
And we're here for you to get your discovery,
不用给我说什么程序
not lecture me on procedure.
我是来演示亚伦先生的
I'm here to demonstrate how Mr. Allen's
盘诘将如何进行的
cross examination's gonna go,
所以给我坐下
now sit the hell down.
亚伦先生  你指证我的委托人
Mr. Allen, what exactly are you getting in return
将得到什么好处
for your testimony against my client?
他将获得自己所犯罪行的豁免权
He's getting immunity for the crimes he committed.
庭上你也打算替他回答吗
Are you gonna answer for him when he's on the stand, too?
你都犯了什么罪
What were those crimes?
我给了威廉・萨特内部交易信息
I gave William Sutter inside information
已经有十余年了
over the course of a decade.
具体是怎么做的
And how, exactly, did you do that?
我的银行得到审查交易的委托
When my bank was hired to review a transaction
我确保交易将发生后
and I determined it was going through,
就电话联系吉尔・米勒
I'd call Jill Miller
告诉她相关方的名字
and I'd give her the relevant names of the parties.
吉尔・米勒  我不明白
Jill Miller? I'm confused.
你跟证监会说
You told the SEC
你是在给威廉・萨特内部信息
that you were feeding William Sutter inside information.
-我们有共识  -和谁
- We had an understanding. - Understood by who?
威廉・萨特
William Sutter.
你和萨特先生有过具体的对话吗
Did you ever have a specific conversation with Mr. Sutter?
你上一次和他见面
I mean, when was the last time
是什么时候
you were even in the same room?
吉尔说他懂的
Jill said that he understood.
胡扯  你根本无法证明威廉知道任何事情
Bullshit, you can't testify William understood anything.
-这叫道听途说  -这是真相
- It's called hearsay. - It's called the truth.
我不管你管它叫什么
I don't give a shit what you call it,
如果你没证据  陪审团就不会采信
if you don't have proof, the jury can never hear it.
你有证据吗
Do you have proof?
我真是不敢相信  你都没有纸面证据吗
Oh, I don't believe this, you don't have a paper trail.
-我有通话记录  -我是说和萨特相关的
- I have the phone records. - I mean to Sutter.
她是他女儿
She's his goddamn daughter!
每个杀人犯也都有父亲
Yeah, and every murderer has a father, too,
但不代表他们父亲就参与了犯罪
doesn't mean they're in on the crime.
你的巧词留到庭上用吧  哈维
Save your metaphors for the trial, Harvey.
现在就免了吧
We don't need them here.
我不需要为上庭留台词
I don't need to save anything for trial
因为你和这个人签的协议是白签了
because you made a deal with this man for nothing,
你给了我个绝好的证人
you handed me my best witness,
这个取证结束了
and this deposition's over.
你个混蛋  你怎么可以这么做
You son of a bitch. How dare you?
做什么  肖恩
How dare I what, Sean?
保护我的委托人吗
Defend my own client?
扯吧  你不是想保护你的委托人
Bullshit, you weren't trying to defend your client.
你是想毁掉我的案子
You were trying to ruin my case
因为你在为迈克的事生气
'cause you're pissed off about Mike.
我当然生气了
I sure as hell am.
我们有协定  你违反了
We had a deal and you broke it.
所以现在我也不打算维护协定了
So now I'm breaking it, too.
我告诉你  哈维
Well, you know what, Harvey?
你要破坏什么协定我都无所谓
I don't care what you're breaking,
因为菲利普・亚伦能让我抓到他女儿
'cause Phillip Allen gets me the daughter
她就能帮我抓到萨特
and that gets me right back to Sutter.
很好  正中我的下怀
Good, 'cause that's exactly what I'd expect you to do.
我理解了
Oh, I get it.
你不是想赢这个案子
You weren't trying to win this thing.
你只是想取消菲利普・亚伦的资格
You just wanted to discredit Phillip Allen
所以我只能再去和迈克交易
so I'd have no choice but to reinstate Mike's deal.
这当然是我希望的了
You're damn right that's what I wanted.
所以与其浪费时间
So instead of getting mad at me
气我做了本该你做的事
for doing what you should have done in the first place,
还不如赶紧加把火
why don't you start turning up the heat
好让迈克逼这个倒霉女人
so Mike can get this goddamn woman
告发她父亲
to turn on her father?
-凯文  -你终于来了
- Kevin. - Oh, good, you're here.
快忙死了
You can help.
我知道你让我保证了不再提起这件事
I know you made me promise not to bring this up again--
-迈克  我说了  -听我说
- Mike, I told you-- - Listen to me.
我跟哈维谈了
I just talked to Harvey.
一个叫菲利普・亚伦的人站出来要作证
A man named Phillip Allen has come forward and he's gonna--
等等  你和哈维说了
Wait, you talked to Harvey?
这个人和卡荷尔做了交易
Listen, this guy cut a deal with Cahill.
懂吗  说明他全都知道
All right? That means he knows all about it.
你要我做什么
What do you want from me?
我要你说服你妻子这事完了
I want you to convince her that this is it.
她只有一个获得赦免权的机会
She has a one-time chance of getting immunity
那就是现在告发她父亲
if she turns on her father now.
你到底怎么知道这个卡荷尔要这么做的
How the hell do you even know this Cahill guy'll do that?
因为我知道他有多想抓萨特
Because I know how bad he wants Sutter,
跟吉尔交易是他的唯一办法
and offering Jill a deal is the best way to make that happen.
但他也有可能保证交易  然后反悔
Or he promises her a deal, then takes it away.
结果就是我的两个孩子在接下来的两年里
And no one's kissing my kids good night
既没有父亲也没有母亲
for the next two years.
哈维不会让这种事发生的
Harvey wouldn't let that happen.
他是威廉的律师
He's William's lawyer.
他不会出卖自己的委托人的
He's not selling out his own client.
你也是他的委托人
You're his client, too.
那不过是为了保护那个给他付账的人
Only to protect the guy who's paying his bills.
他才不在乎我呢
He doesn't give a shit about me.
也许确实如此  但他在乎我
Maybe not, but he does give a shit about me!
你什么  你是什么意思
What're you-- what're you saying?
我是说吉尔要是交易
I'm saying that offering Jill a deal
不止她一个人不用坐牢
doesn't just get her out of prison.
我也能出狱
It gets me out, too.
你在告我的密  迈克
You've been informing on me, Mike?
是的
Yes.
别让我看见你  你这个叛徒
Get the hell out of my sight, you traitor piece of shit.
凯文  听着  我告诉你
Kevin, listen, I'm only telling you this
是为了让你明白
so that you'll see--
明白什么  明白你有多混蛋吗
See what? How full of shit you are?
告诉我你小时候就失去了双亲
Telling me you grew up without a mom and dad
也只是为了获取我的信任吧
just to gain my trust--
不是这样的
That is not why I did that.
而且我现在告诉你实话
And I just told you the truth
是为了让你相信我在意你
so that you trust that I care about you.
胡扯  因为你现在
Bullshit, 'cause here you are,
就是要让两个孩子失去双亲
willing to leave two little kids all alone
只为了你自己能出狱
just to get your goddamn freedom.
-凯文  我很抱歉  -还没到你抱歉的时候
- Kevin, I'm sorry-- - No, you're not.
但你马上就会了
But you're about to be.
来啊  还击啊  你个叛徒
Come on, fight! Fight back, you traitor!
-打我啊  -你听我说
- Fight me back! - You have to listen to me!
来啊  打啊
Come on, fight!
-这事没完  迈克  -赶快把他带走
- This isn't done, Mike! - Get him out of here now!
-不  不  不  -单独监禁
- No, no, no-- - Get him to solitary now!
不  不要单独监禁  这是我的错
No, not solitary! It's my fault, it's my fault!
-你们不用这样  -罗斯  罗斯
- You don't have to do this! - Ross, Ross!
再说一个字  你也去单独监禁
Another word, and you're going to solitary, too.
我是哈维・斯佩克特
Harvey Specter.
丹伯里联邦监狱有人向你致电
You have a call from Danbury Federal Prison.
你愿意承担费用吗
Do you accept the charges?
-愿意  -哈维
- Yes. - Harvey.
迈克  太好了
Mike, good.
我完成了我的任务  我解决菲利普・亚伦了
I did my part and I took care of Phillip Allen.
告诉我你完成了你让凯文说服妻子的任务
Tell me you did yours and got Kevin to talk to his wife.
我试过了
I tried.
但我把他弄进单独监禁了
Instead, I got him put in solitary.
什么  到底什么情况
What? How the hell did that happen?
我告诉他我一直在出卖他
I told him I was informing on him
然后他开始玩命揍我
and then he started beating the shit out of me.
你逗我呢  你为什么要告诉他
Are you kidding me? Why would you do that?
因为撒谎解决不了问题
Because lying wasn't getting it done
而我现在没那么多时间
and I'm living on borrowed time,
所以我觉得还是告诉他好了
so I thought I might as well tell him, anyway.
那你最好想办法把他弄出来
Then you better figure out a way to get him out of there,
因为我们得赶在卡荷尔之前
because we need to get Jill to turn on Sutter
说服吉尔告发萨特
before Cahill gets her to.
这就是我打给你的原因
That's why I'm calling you.
我已经有办法了  我只想知道
I already have a way, I just need to know
你完成了另一件你该做的事
you did that other thing you were supposed to do.
给加洛弄到了保释听证会
I need to know you got Gallo his parole hearing.
开始吧
Let's get to it.
情况如何
What happened?
好消息
Good news.
法庭准许了我们的动议
The court granted our motion.
他们把你的处决延后了一个月
They pushed your execution back a month.
我不敢相信
I don't believe it.
你们说服了我伯母我没杀那些人吗
You convinced my aunt I didn't kill those people?
-不  伦纳德  我没说服她  -我不懂
- No, Leonard, I didn't. - I don't understand.
你说她得到场的
You said that she had to agree to be there for me.
她同意签字
She agreed to sign the papers.
但她不会来
But she's not gonna come.
该死
Goddamn it.
伦纳德  别偏离重点
Leonard, don't take your eye off the ball.
这只是为了给我们争取时间
This was about buying us time.
你说我偏离重点
Take my eye off the ball?
你到底在不在乎我
Do you even give a shit about me?
我们当然在乎
Of course we do.
是  我知道你在乎
Yeah, I know you do.
但我想知道她在不在乎
But I want to know if she cares
我的生死
whether I live or die.
我刚把你的处决延后了
I just got your execution pushed back.
我问的不是这个
That's not what I asked you.
你都没去看她  对不对
You didn't even go see her, did you?
我要管理公司
I have a firm to run.
我们两个人中只要一个人拿到她的签名就行
And only one of us needed to get her signature.
但你们两个人本可以说服她
But two of you could've helped convince her
我是无辜的
that I'm innocent.
你不明白吗
Don't you get it?
抚养我长大的女人不想和我有任何瓜葛
The woman who raised me wants nothing to do with me.
伦纳德  我知道你很失望
Leonard, I know you're disappointed.
但我的职责
But it's not my job
不是帮你修复你和你姨妈之间的关系
to repair your relationship with your aunt.
我的职责是把你从这里弄出去
It's my job to get you out of here.
我根本就出不去了
I ain't never getting out of here!
你不明白吗
Don't you understand that?
你去和法庭周旋吧
So you go play your game with the courts.
但不管是三十天还是六十天  都无所谓
But whether it's 30 days or 60 days, it doesn't matter,
因为我会死在这里的  女士
'cause I'm gonna die in here, lady.
我只要求你做一件事  你都没做到
The one thing I asked you to do, you didn't.
你甚至都没有尝试一下
You didn't even care enough to try.
走吧
Just get out.
你最好是来告诉我我有听证会了
You better be here to tell me I have a hearing.
这就是我想跟你说的
That's exactly what I'm here to tell you.
但在你帮我干件事之前
But you're not gonna have anything
你什么都没有
unless you do something for me.
扯淡  我们协议里没这条
Bullshit. Wasn't part of the deal.
我才不管
I don't give a shit.
我受够了你总是威胁我
I'm tired of you threatening me,
如果你想有一丝提前离开这里的机会
so if you even want a chance of getting out of here early,
你得先给我干件事
you're gonna do something for me.
顺便跟你说
And by the way,
现在跟凯文说我告发他有点晚了
it's too late to tell Kevin that I've been informing on him.
我已经告诉他了
I already did.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我要你把他从单独监禁里弄出来
I need you to get him out of solitary.
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding me, right?
-我办不了  -扯淡
- I can't do that - That's bullshit.
我来的第一晚你就能换进我的牢房
You switched into my cell the first night and ever since,
从那时起你就一直吹嘘你在这里能干什么
you've been bragging about everything that you can do in here,
你还是别再跟我说你干不了
so how about you stop telling me that you can't do it,
就告诉我你到底干不干
and just tell me whether or not you will.
好吧  小迈克
All right, Mikey.
我给你搞到离开单独监禁的机会
I'll get your ticket to freedom out of solitary for you.
但如果你离开这里而我没有
But if you get out of here and I don't,
你要知道  在外面和在里面一样
you should know, i can get to you
我都能易如反掌地搞定你
just as easily out there as I can in here.
我说的"搞定你"
And when I say "Get to you,"
你要记得当初我做了什么
You got to remember what I did
才让哈维把我关在这里的
to make Harvey put me away in the first place.
你想谈谈监狱里的事情吗
Do you want to talk about what happened at the prison?
不  瑞秋  我不想
No, Rachel, I don't.
因为不管伦纳德信不信
Because whether Leonard believes me or not,
-我确实要管理公司  -我知道
- I really do have a firm to run. - I know you do.
那你应该知道今晚我离开这里之前
Then you know I have ten other things to do
还有很多其他事要完成
before I get out of here tonight.
那我就不管它了
Then I will leave it alone.
但不管怎样  受害人的父亲对我破口大骂时
But for what it's worth, you were there for me
是你关心我支持我
when the victim's father lashed out at me.
因此
And so,
如果你想找个人谈谈
if you want to talk about it with someone,
我只想告诉你  我也关心你
I just want you to know that I'm here for you, too.
谢谢你  瑞秋
I appreciate that, Rachel.
但现在  我更想让你把时间花在
But right now, I'd rather you spend your time
想办法让伦纳德・贝利出狱上
finding something to get Leonard Bailey out.
我会的
I will.
你好
Hello?
你好  杰夫  是我
Hi, Jeff, it's me.
今天晚上我们吃个饭如何
How would you like to have dinner with me tonight?
乐意奉陪  杰西卡
I would love to, Jessica.
告诉我地点就行
Just name the place.
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
上次和你来过以后我就再没有来过这里
I just haven't been in this place since I was here with you.
我记得你很喜欢这里
I remembered how much you liked it.
你为什么给我打电话
So how come you decided to call me?
你说你还没准备好
You said you were still in it.
你曾经跟我说过
You told me once
你相信事出皆有因
that you think maybe things happen for a reason.
你是指今天碰到我吗
You mean running into me today?
我是指那之后发生的事
I mean after I ran into you.
我基本上被指责为冷酷
I was pretty much accused of being cold,
无情且漠不关心
heartless, and uncaring.
如果是律师同行这么说我  我倒能接受
And I can take it when it's lawyers saying that about me.
但这个评价却是来自我正在救的人
But this was from the man whose life I'm trying to save.
所以你想跟一个了解
And you wanted to be with someone
你另一面的人待一会儿
who knows a different side of you.
我觉得我想跟某位知道
I thought I wanted to be with someone
那一面完全不是我的人待一会儿
who knows that's not a side of me at all.
杰西卡  我曾跟你说过我爱过你
Jessica, I told you I loved you once.
我说那句话的时候
And when I said that,
我想表达的是我爱你的其中一点
I meant that one of the things that I love about you
就是你那种能把感情放在一边
is your ability to push emotion aside
令对手满地找牙的能力
and knock the shit out of people.
所以你认为我是冷酷  但你却爱我这一点
So you think I'm cold, but you love that about me?
我是说那是我爱你的其中一点
I'm saying that's one of the things that I love about you.
另外一点是  在你的内心
The other thing is that in your heart,
你一点都不冷酷
you're not cold at all.
晚饭后怎么说  你带我回家吗
What do you say after dinner, you take me home?
我想说
I say...
我觉得我们这次应该慢慢来
I think that we should take it slow this time.
听着  我知道你现在很恨我
Listen, I know you hate me right now,
但现在这一刻
but right this second,
我们是同一战线的
we are on the same side.
我知道
I know.
-真的吗  -是的
- You do? - Yeah.
因为他们刚我从单独监禁中放出来
'Cause they just let me out of solitary,
然而我去打电话给吉尔
and I went to call Jill.
我本打算跟她全盘托出的
I was gonna tell her everything,
但在我有机会这么做之前
but before I got a chance to do that...
她跟我说她被起诉了
she told me she was indicted.
-凯文  我很抱歉  -我不需要道歉  迈克
- Kevin, I'm so sorry. - I don't need sorrys, Mike.
我需要找到个办法让我妻子免受牢狱之灾
I need to find a way to keep my wife out of prison.
-那就让我帮你  -你可以帮我
- Then let me help you. - You can help me.
但不能是试图让她指证她父亲的方法
But it can't be by trying to get her to turn on him,
因为我告诉你
because I'm telling you,
她是绝对没有可能会那么做的
there is no way in hell she's gonna do that.
你真的觉得她也愿意为了他进监狱吗
You really think she's willing to go to prison for him, too?
我发现她和她父亲这事的那天晚上
Look, the night I found out about her and her father,
我问她怎么能被卷进
I asked her how she could have gotten involved
这种事情里
in something like this.
原来  她发现他父亲的
Turns out, she found out
整个商业帝国就是场庞氏骗局
his whole place was a Ponzi scheme.
她对他大发雷霆
She flipped out on him
然后他跟她讲了个关于收益
and he gave her some bullshit sob story
是如何日益减少的狗屁悲伤故事
about how the returns were running dry.
他跟她说如果她能弄到内幕消息
He told her that if she got inside information for him,
只要一次  就能让他们免遭失去一切的厄运
one time, it'd keep them from losing eveverything.
而等她回过神来  收手已经来不及了
And the next thing she knew, it was too late to stop.
是的  他欺骗了她
Yeah, he tricked her.
而当我试图跟她说的时候
And when I tried to tell her that,
让她和我一起退出  你知道她说什么吗
get her to quit with me, you know what she said?
她说她绝不会那么做的
She said she'd never do that.
因为不管他在生意场上是怎么做的
Because no matter what he did with the business,
她都知道他会愿意为她赴汤蹈火
she knew he was willing to run into a burning building for her.
所以她也愿意为他做同样的事
So she was willing to do the same for him.
凯文  我需要你把手机给我用一下
Kevin, I need you to let me use your cell phone.
我需要你相信我
I need you to trust me.
-哈维・斯佩克特办公室  -唐娜  是我
- Harvey Specter's office. - Donna, it's me.
我需要你帮忙  我时间不多
I need your help and I don't have much time.
你需要我做什么
What do you need?
我觉得我有办法让吉尔说出实情了
I think I have a plan to get Jill to talk.
迈克  你难道不应该跟哈维说吗
Mike, shouldn't you be telling Harvey about this?
我等下就打给他
I'm calling him next.
但无论我们怎么做  除非你能先让她不抗拒
But whatever we do, we are not gonna be able
否则我们都没法让她说出实情的
to get her to talk unless you first get her to listen.
塔拉  我知道我4分钟前才打过电话
Hey Tara, I know I called four minutes ago
我也知道你说七点整
and I know you said 7:00 p.m. sharp,
但我现在觉得你说的是不是七点多
but now I'm thinking you said 7:00 P.M. short.
我不知道为什么会那样
And I don't know exactly why that would be,
但现在7点12分了  我就想
uh, but it's 7:12, and I'm just wondering what--
喂
Hello?
该死
Goddamn it.
路易
Louis.
我刚看到你打了两个电话给我
I just saw you called two times.
-很抱歉我迟到了  -塔拉  不用
- I'm so sorry I'm late. - Tara, please.
无需道歉
There's no need to apologize.
我让他们多保留预订15分钟
I had them hold the reservation for 15 minutes,
现在才13分钟  我相信一定没问题的
and it's only been 13 minutes, so I'm sure it'll be fine.
谢谢  路易
Thank you, Louis.
利特预订那桌的客人到齐了
The Litt party is ready.
好极了  有桌子空出来我就安排你们入座
Awesomeness, I'll have a table for you as soon as one's ready.
有桌子空出来
As soon as one's ready?
我让你保留预订15分钟
I asked you to hold our reservation for 15 minutes
现在才过去13分钟  你这个嬉皮士混蛋
and it's only been 13 minutes, you hipster douche bag.
打扰一下  先生  一切都还好吗
Excuse me, sir, is everything okay?
不  一切都不好
No, everything is not okay,
这个混蛋把我订的桌子给了别人
this asshole gave away my table.
哥们  没事的  我再给你安排张桌子
Hey, man, it's all good. I'll get you another table.
"哥们"  非常有事
"Hey, man," it's all bad.
我不要其他桌子  我就要我订的那桌
I don't want another table. I want the one I reserved.
所以你为什么不去告诉那些人
So why don't you tell those people that you gave them
你给了他们属于别人的位置
something that belongs to someone else,
因为我是不会跟另一个男人分享
'cause I'm not going to share the most exquisite table
这个星球上最精美的餐桌的
on the planet with another man.
路易
Louis.
这行不通
This isn't gonna work.
路易  路易  跟我说说
Louis--Louis. Please talk to me.
听着  我知道我说过我能接受这事
Look, I know I said I'd be okay with this,
但事实上我并不能接受
but I'm not okay.
因为我联系不到你的时候
Because the whole time I couldn't reach you,
我就会不停的想你是在和他打电话
I kept thinking that you were on the phone with him
和他有说有笑你侬我侬
and laughing with him and loving him.
而只要你还有其他男人
And as long as you have another man,
我就会一直认为你跟他在一起
I'm always gonna think that you're with him,
你在想着他
thinking about him--
-路易  那  -让我说完
- Louis? That's-- - Let me finish.
你是我这辈子见过最吸引我的女人
You are the most riveting woman I've ever met.
我中了你的魔法
You've cast a spell on me.
我永远不会跟你说你该怎么生活
And I would never tell you how to live your life.
但我不会跟其他男人分享你
But I will not share you with another man.
而且我不理解为什么会有任何男人愿意
And I don't understand why any man would.
我想要你  我想要你的全部
I want you, and I want all of you.
-但如果我不能拥有  -路易
- But if I can't have that-- - Louis?
带我回家
Take me home.
来  让我帮你一把
Here, let me help you with that.
-真的吗  -当然
- Oh, would you? - Of course.
红发女孩必须得团结
Us redheads have to stick together.
-谢谢  -别客气  吉尔
- Thank you. - You're welcome, Jill.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是骗你进丹伯里联邦监狱的女人
I'm the woman who tricked you into going to Danbury.
我跟你无话可说
I have nothing to say to you.
请听我说完  我亲自过来就是因为我不想
Please, I came here in person because I don't want to
再骗你一次
trick you again.
那要说什么就赶紧说吧
Then say whatever it is you're here to say.
我来跟你说我父亲的事
I'm here to tell you about my father.
他好几年前被判有罪  在定罪之前
He committed a crime years ago, and before he did,
他试图拉我跟他一起承担后果
he tried to get me to put my toe in the water with him.
我拒绝了  但我当时差点答应了
I said no, but I almost said yes,
因为我爱他
because I loved him.
我知道他是个好人
And I knew he was a good man.
你想让我怎么做
What do you want from me?
就跟我上次想让你做的一样
Same thing that I wanted the last time.
我希望你明天去监狱看你丈夫
I want you to visit your husband in prison tomorrow.
我希望你能放下心结
And I want you to keep an open mind.
路易  我知道你很有激情
Louis, I knew you were passionate,
但我没想到你这么有激情
but I had no idea how passionate.
简直太魔幻了
That was magic.
我很为我的成果自豪
Yeah, I take pride in my work.
应该的
Well, you should.
既然这样  过十五分钟马上要上演
Well, in that case, there's another show starting
下一场好戏了
in about 15 minutes.
你知道我是什么意思吧
Okay, you know what that means, don't you?
你会累坏的
You're gonna be exhausted,
也就是说你今天要在我家过夜了
which means you're gonna have to spend the night.
那不如白天也不走了
Well, then what do you say we make the whole day of it, too?
你有什么打算
What exactly do you have in mind?
梅特剧院明天有场《塞维利亚的理发师》彩排
There's a dress rehearsal of the "Barber of Seville"
我能弄到资助商席位
at the Met tomorrow and I could get us in as patrons.
路易
Louis...
我十分乐意
I would love to.
-威廉  我们得谈谈  -我不是已经来了
- William, we need to talk. - I'm here, just like you asked.
他们起诉了你的女儿
They indicted your daughter.
我知道  她告诉我了
I know. She told me.
我告诉你  你利用她做挡箭牌
And I told you, you were playing a dangerous game
是在玩火
using her to shield you.
吉尔是大姑娘了
Jill's a big girl.
她能照顾好自己
She can take care of herself.
照顾好自己还是照顾好你
Take care of herself, or take care of you?
你是想说我做了什么坏事吗
Are you accusing me of something?
我不是想  我是在告诉你
I'm not accusing you, I'm telling you,
你应该醒一醒了
you need to wake the hell up.
你说什么
What did you just say to me?
你知道吉尔被传讯后卡荷尔准备干什么吗
Do you know what Cahill's gonna do once Jill's arraigned?
不管需要关她多久他就不会手软的
He's gonna sit her down for as long as it takes
直到她接受协议把你供出来
until she cuts a deal to give you up.
她不会这么做的
She would never do that.
你不知道等他们把她关进那间屋子里后
You have no idea what she'll do when they get her
她会做什么
into that room.
我告诉你  如果我的废物女婿
And I'm telling you, if my loser of
都没有屈服  那吉尔肯定也不会
a son-in-law didn't cave, then Jill sure as hell won't.
听我说  该死
Listen to me, goddamn it.
这跟凯文的情况不一样
This isn't gonna be what it was like it was with Kevin.
你想让我怎么样  哈维
What do you want from me, Harvey?
我想让你允许我
I want you to give me authorization
为你们俩提供协议
to cut you both a deal.
你自首  可能只要关上三年
You turn yourself in, you get maybe three years,
而她也不用入狱
and you keep her out.
我为什么要那么做
Why the hell would I do that?
因为如果她供出你  你的刑期
Because if she turns on you, you're gonna be getting
可不止这么点了
a hell of a lot more.
我不会接受的
I'm not cutting a deal.
你以为你这么对待你的女儿
And you think if you're willing to do this
她就不会这么对你吗
to your own daughter, she won't be willing to do it to you?
吉尔还年轻  我已经老了
Jill's a young woman, I'm an old man.
她坐个几年牢根本没什么损失
She does a few years, it hardly makes a dent.
等她出来  还是可以打网球
When she gets out, she can still play tennis
做普拉提之类花我的钱
and go to Pilates and do all the things
玩的玩意儿
I always gave her the money to do.
你早就知道事情会演变成这样
You knew it might come to this, didn't you?
萨特供词
我爱我的女儿  哈维
I love my daughter, Harvey,
但没有我  她什么都不是
but she'd be nothing without me.
她也知道她只要替我坐牢
And she knows if she does this for me,
她下半辈子就不用愁了
she'll be taken care of for the rest of her life.
就这样  你不接受
So that's it? No deal?
不接受
No deal.
我很抱歉  吉尔
I'm sorry, Jill.
我要接受协议
I want to cut a deal.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
是的
Yes.
你能帮我吗
Can you do that for me?
不行
No, I can't.
为什么
Why not?
因为他代表你父亲
Because he represents your father.
但我不是
But I don't.
所以我可以
So I can.
塔拉  今天真是不能更棒了
Tara, I didn't think today could get any better,
我不知道你对水压做了什么
but whatever you did to that water pressure
但感觉太好了  我从来没感觉如此焕然一新
is thing of beauty. I haven't felt this fresh
-干干净净  -路易  我要和你谈谈
- and clean since-- - Louis, I have to talk to you.
-怎么了  -约书亚来了电话
- What is it? - Joshua called.
他明天要来城里住两天
He's coming to town tomorrow for two days.
我以为昨晚过后  你们俩
But after last night, I thought it was over
已经结束了
between the two of you?
路易
Louis...
我们在一起很多年  我不能就这么不见他
we've been together for years. I can't just not see him.
你要跟他分手吗
So you're gonna break up with him?
我不知道
I don't know.
欢迎来到丹伯里  肖恩
Welcome to Danbury, Sean.
你现在可是冒着我会被人认出来
You know you're taking a big risk that someone's gonna
并发现你想干什么的风险
recognize me and figure out that you're up to something.
要是我不亲自把这个交给你
Well, I'd be taking an even bigger risk
我面临的风险更大
if I didn't hand this to you personally.
这次你不能取消我的协议了
You're not gonna weasel out of my deal again.
这是什么
What is this?
这是你的办公和吉尔・米勒
That is an iron clad agreement between your office
定下的协议
and Jill Miller.
-你现在代理吉尔・米勒了  -是的
- You're representing Jill Miller now? - Yes, I am.
她知道你不是律师吗
Does she know that you're not a lawyer?
她知道
She does.
她觉得没关系  因为是我
And she's okay with it because I'm also the guy
让她免除了牢狱之灾
who's keeping her out of prison.
我直接把内容告诉你吧
Let me save you the trouble of reading that.
这上面说她愿意指证她的父亲
It says that she's gonna testify against her father,
接受无争辩答辩  获得完全赦免权
pleads no contest, and receives full immunity.
但这上面也说你承认
But it also says that you acknowledge that
是我把她带来找你的
I brought her to you.
那我就拿回办公室再签字吧
Well, then I better bring it to my office and sign it.
不管你在不在意
Oh, and for what it's worth,
我没有试图取消你的协议
I didn't try to weasel out of your deal.
为了让它不被取消我真的尽力了
I did everything I could to keep it in place.
现在它不会被取消了
Well, now it's back in place.
因为我把你需要的东西都给你了
Because I just gave you everything that you need.
不  迈克  你还什么都没给我
No, Mike, you didn't give me everything yet.
因为我还需要把威廉・萨特关进监狱
Because what I still need is William Sutter behind bars.
你干了什么
What the hell did you do?
很高兴见到你  威廉  想喝点什么吗
Nice to see you, William. Can I get you a drink?
你以为我不会发现你录下了我们的谈话
You think I wouldn't find out that you recorded me
然后放给我女儿听了吗
and played it for my daughter?
我没有放给她听
I didn't play it for her.
我放给了我另一名委托人  凯文・米勒
I played it for my other client, Kevin Miller.
只是我在播放的时候吉尔碰巧也在那
Jill just happened to be there when I did.
她现在要告发我了
And now she's turning on me.
那看来她并像你想的那样愿意等五年
Then I guess it turns out she didn't want to wait five years
再去打网球
to play more tennis like you thought.
真该死
Goddamn it,
你违反了律师与当事人的信息披露豁免权
you broke attorney-client privilege.
我没有违反任何条例  威廉
I didn't break anything, William.
因为我刚跟你说完  凯文也是我的委托人
Because like I just told you, Kevin's my client too,
我有义务让他了解实情
and I had an obligation to share the facts with him.
所以你不但不该攻击我  还应该感谢我
So instead of attacking me, you should be thanking me.
因为我去找了卡荷尔并且帮你达成了
Because I went to Cahill and cut you the best deal
你所能得到的最好的交易
you're ever gonna get.
你为什么要这么对我
Why would you do this to me?
这是你自己一手造成的  威廉
You did this to yourself, William.
你让我同时代理你和凯文
You had me represent both you and Kevin,
这意味着我必须在两名委托人间进行选择
which means I had to choose between two clients.
你自己也说过
And you said it, yourself.
你上了年纪  而他们是一对年轻夫妇
You're an old man, and they're a young couple,
所以我选择了他们而没选你
and I chose them over you.
我没让你代理我们两个人
I didn't have you represent us both.
这主意是你想的
It was your idea.
我想好像是的  不是么
I guess it was, wasn't it?
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
你设计坑我
You set me up!
我保证让这件事人尽皆知
And I'm gonna make sure the world knows it.
你可以告诉任何人任何事  威廉
You can tell the world anything you want, William.
但是你没有证据并且即使要讲
But you've got no proof and you'll be telling it
你也只能在牢里讲
from behind bars.
总之  我劝你还是签字同意这笔交易
Either way, I suggest you sign this deal,
因为这对你来说已经是最划算的了
'cause it's the best you're ever gonna get.
杰西卡
Jessica.
你怎么来了
What're you doing here?
我昨晚过得很愉快
I had a great time last night.
我本来是要给你打电话约你下周再出来
And I was going to call you about going out again next week
因为我知道你想慢慢来
because I know you want to take it slow.
但随即我明白了你想要慢慢来
But then I found out that you want to take it slow
其实是因为你可能要走了
because you may not be here much longer.
你怎么知道的
How'd you find out?
他们打电话向我征询意见
They called for a reference.
你怎么跟他们说的
And what'd you tell them?
我说能有你是他们的福气
I said them they'd be lucky to have you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
因为我没确定要不要接受
Because I wasn't sure I was gonna take it.
但现在你确定了
But now you are.
杰西卡  如果我认为还有那么一点机会
Jessica, if I thought there would be a chance
你会跟我一起走  我早就问你了
in the world that you would come with me, I would've asked you.
但我们都知道那是不可能的
But we both know that's not gonna happen.
因为你告诉我事情还没结束
Because you told me it's not over yet,
但你的意思是永远不会结束
but what you meant is that it's never gonna be over.
这可是我的事务所  杰夫
It's my firm, Jeff.
这是我耗尽毕生精力所建立起来的
It's the thing I spent my whole life building.
我没有为此指责你
And I'm not judging you for it.
你一直保持真我
You are who you are,
我爱的也正是这样的你
and I love who you are.
我一直想着要重返芝加哥
But I've been thinking about going back to Chicago
虽然再次和你邂逅
for a long time now, and as much as seeing you again
让我很想留下
makes me want to stay here...
但我不得不这么做
This is something I have to do.
就像我说的
Like I said.
有你是他们的福气
They're lucky to have you.
搞定了
It's done.
萨特接受交易
Sutter took the deal.
吉尔安全了
Jill's safe.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
我
I'm, uh...
很抱歉让吉尔听到那段录音
I'm sorry that Jill had to hear what she heard.
那是唯一的办法  伙计
It was the only way, man.
再说  你也没说什么
Besides, you didn't say it.
是啊  但在我同意告发你时
No, but I did know what I was doing
我确实知道接下来我要做什么
when I agreed to inform on you.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你不该承受这些
You didn't deserve any of that.
你瞧  我们第一次见面时
Hey, look, when we first met,
我就让加洛进来了
I let Gallo in here.
那和你对我做的事一样都是背叛
And that was as much a betrayal as what you did to me.
但你当时并不认识我
Yeah, but you didn't know me.
而我是认识你的
I knew you.
干嘛  你是想让我恨你吗
What, are you trying to make me hate you?
不是
No.
只是我要出狱了而你却不能
It's just that I'm getting out and you're not.
是的  我没法出去
No, I'm not.
但你让我妻子免受牢狱之灾
But you kept my wife out of prison,
在我看来  我们已经扯平了
and as far as I'm concerned, that makes us square.
谢谢你凯文
Thank you, Kevin.
你要去哪
Where you going?
我吗
Me?
我要给你几分钟享受下
I'm gonna give you a few minutes to enjoy the fact
你要出狱的喜悦
that you're getting out.
然后再打个电话告诉瑞秋
And to call Rachel and tell her.
唐娜  我想到了一个好主意
Donna, I'm on to something.
我只需要点时间把东西写下来
I just need one second to write it down.
怎么了  什么事你这么高兴
What is it? What're you so happy about?
我想我找到能让
I think I just figured out a way
伦纳德・贝利的案件得以重审的办法了
to get Leonard Bailey's case reopened.
瑞秋  这太棒了
Rachel, this is amazing.
来吧  拿上你的东西
Come on, get your things.
我们可以路上边走边聊
We can talk about it on the way out.
因为我们要去庆祝一下
Because we're going to celebrate.
不了  这是好消息  但还不至于要庆祝
No, it's good news, but I'm not ready to celebrate.
你当然要庆祝
Yes, you are.
因为我不是在说你的案子
Because I'm not talking about your case.
瑞秋  哈维和迈克成功了
Rachel, Harvey and Mike did it.
迈克就要出狱了
Mike's getting out.
什么
What?
你听到的没错
You heard me.
他们成功了
They did it.
萨特要进监狱了  意味着迈克能回家了
Sutter's going away, which means Mike's coming home.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
天哪
Oh, God.
来吧  趁你还是单身的时候
Come on, let's go have some fun
我们去找点乐子
while you're still single.
迈克打来的
It's Mike.
你好
Hello?
是我
Hey, it's me.
我知道是你
I know it's you.
结束了
It's over.
我可以回家了
I'm coming home.
我刚听说了
I just heard.
天哪  我好爱你
God, I love you so much.
我也爱你
I love you, too.